{
    "id": "7b0ce54dbe534faa93bd145b059c62ec",
    "title": "Present participle or past participle",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c65cdf8dd91b4cfc90b3ee6ae2983159",
            "title": "Present Participle Or Past Participle",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The film was so …………………… that I fell asleep in the middle.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "boring",
                        "bored"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Would you like to come over? I’m so ……………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "boring",
                        "bored"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The journey was quite ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "tiring",
                        "tired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her behavior was quite …………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "disgusting",
                        "disgusted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She left in a hurry because she was …………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "disgusting",
                        "disgusted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ……………………. everyone by turning up late.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "annoyed",
                        "annoying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was really …………………. by her story.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "inspired",
                        "inspiring"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her story was so …………………….. that they decided to publish it as a book.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "inspiring",
                        "inspired"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was very ……………………… with his results.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "pleased",
                        "pleasing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We were …………………… to hear that there had been an accident.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "shocked",
                        "shocking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}